Samsung Electronics is continuing its so-called "
diss war" targeting Apple.
Following Samsung Electronics' U.S. subsidiary, which opened the fire on the diss battle,
Samsung Electronics' New Zealand subsidiary
has also joined in the wordplay marketing.  On the
11th, Samsung Electronics New Zealand revealed
on its official Instagram a promotional item held by a man with the same name as former CEO Tim Apple on the
Galaxy G
Pole Day
.  The advertisement
prominently featured the name "Team" and included the phrase that Palmerston North's
team had switched to Galaxy phones
.  It is designed to make it seem as though Cook
chose the Galaxy instead of the iPhone
.  Next up
is major news from Samsung Electronics.
After saying that the team switched to Galaxy phones, that is
correct.  It is none other than Tim Cook.
They revealed that they share the same name, stating that it is Palmester North's team.  He then indirectly targeted Apple by adding, "Which Tim Cook were you
thinking of?"
Samsung Electronics'
offensive against Apple is continuing in the United States as well
.  Samsung Electronics U.S. Mobile Official
X account will be folding up here around the time of Apple's unveiling of the foldable iPhone
Duo
.
Apple posted messages asking to be notified when the rehash was finished, conveying a message that it had belatedly caught up with Samsung's foldable technology
.  Some posts recorded
millions to over ten million views and even
directly encouraged switching to Galaxy through hashtags when switching
.  Samsung Electronics has
expanded its targets of attack to include product names and accessories.  Regarding the name "Duo," they
tagged the Duolingo account and
pointed out that they had copied theirs, and also criticized iPhone
accessories, saying they
felt like having only sauce and no food.   no see
.
[Music]